Get ready.
Your brain is
about to get
stronger.
Ready for today's
"wit" workout
if someone says,
You're not very
good at this,
are you?
QUICK!
What's your comeback?
OPTION A)
Well,
I'm better at
it than you
are at being
polite.
OPTION B)
I'm practicing selective
excellence.
OPTION C)
Good enough to
know when someone's
fishing for attention.
The truth is
there is no
right answer.
All are valid
comebacks.
The key to
this exercise is
speed.
When you're fast
and precise with
your responses to
offensive remarks,
then people will
find you witty.
Your challenge for
the day is
to practice comebacks.
When someone throws
shade your way,
don't freeze,
but respond quickly.
You'll get more
accurate with your
responses the more
you practice.
Follow for more
daily wit workouts.